(upbeat music)
♪ Yeah, one, two princes
kneel before you ♪
♪ That's what I said now ♪
♪ Princes, princes who adore you ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ One has diamonds in his pockets ♪
♪ That's some bread, now ♪
♪ This one said he wants
to buy you rockets ♪
♪ Ain't in his head, now ♪
♪ Eh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Di, di, bip, bip, di, bip, bip, bip ♪
♪ Be, be, bip, bipidip ♪
♪ Buduba, dubba, dubba,
dubba, dubba, dubba, dubba ♪
♪ This one got a princely racket ♪
♪ That's what I said now ♪
♪ Got some big seal upon his jacket ♪
♪ Ain't in his head now ♪
♪ You marry him, your
father will condone you ♪
♪ How 'bout that now ♪
♪ You marry me, your
father will disown you ♪
♪ He'll eat his hat, now ♪
♪ Marry him or marry me ♪
♪ I'm the one that loved
you baby can't you see ♪
♪ I ain't got no future or family tree ♪
♪ But I know what a prince
and lover ought to be ♪
♪ I know what a prince
and lover ought be ♪
♪ Said if you want to call me baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to tell me maybe ♪
♪ And if you want to buy me flowers ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to talk for hours ♪
(rock music)
♪ Said one, two princes kneel before you ♪
♪ That what I said now ♪
♪ Princes, princes who adore you ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ One has diamonds in his pockets ♪
♪ And that's some bread, now ♪
♪ This one, he wants to buy you rockets ♪
♪ Ain't in his head, now ♪
♪ Marry him or marry me ♪
♪ I'm the one that loved
you baby can't you see ♪
♪ I ain't got no future or family tree ♪
♪ But I know what a prince
and lover ought to be ♪
♪ I know what a prince
and lover ought be ♪
♪ Said if you want to call me baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to tell me maybe ♪
♪ And if you wanted to buy me flowers ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to talk for hours ♪
♪ And if you want to call me baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to tell me maybe ♪
♪ And if you like to buy me flowers ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to talk for hours ♪
♪ If you want to call me baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to tell me maybe ♪
♪ If you want to buy me flowers ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ And if you like to talk for hours ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Just, just go ahead now ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ Oh, your majesty ♪
♪ Come on forget the king and marry me ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on and ♪
♪ Go ahead now ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪
♪ If you want to buy me flowers ♪
♪ Go ahead now ♪
♪ Yeah, just go ahead now, baby ♪
♪ Just go ahead now ♪